You guys had to end my life to go to somebody else's lives for no reason.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
I'm doing the versions well, I'm just kidding, I'm eating, like, actually, Katie.
Hello?
Hi, Sher Sher.
I ended my life to go over the psyche to get backstage, crazy.
One of these people will learn to be a little bit more grateful, I will never know.
I think we just have to teach them to like hard way.
I like just chilling here, page was up here, we're having a really good time.
Um, Paige was playing like, we were just having a really good time now, but hey guys, thank you live and somebody said he's live and I said let's go to them support.
Went over there, picked me off for some nonsense. Um, you know, allowed people up there that are doxing some really nice people, but I guess that's the way it goes.
I'm back to my little corner.
We'll get it together though.
Imagine like, um,
ending your panel with a whole bunch of people
taking over there, like, and then that motherfucker gets coffee.
Hmm.
She's absolutely...
Has like he doesn't even know what the fuck is going on. It's the dumbest fucking game ever
Well, we're good. We're gonna get it back together
We can play trivia here. We can do a battle rap like we do we can talk our fuck shit
and we can do everything that can be done everywhere else without
You know
having people just like
I don't know playing with I can I mean I can like rap about that can sing about it
But I would I don't want to just on that hard. I think I should though
Nick you don't even go live if you go live
Remember this, you can always restream me, okay?
And if you go live and you have a panel,
I'll be right there.
I'll be the first person to fucking come on your panel
and I will like restream you
and I will post your channel there,
but you just gotta tell me, all right?
I'll do that for you, that's not a big deal.
I just don't want to bring like negative V or like a bullshit to your fucking neck of the woods, but
You know, it's not a big deal
My last channel I promoted almost everybody I just like right now
I'm a little bit more careful because I don't want to bring like bad or negative energy to other people's channels, but
Of course, I will do that
I promise I'll be right there if you go live right now and the live and then I'll go over to yours
And I promise you you want to start a life?
I'll share your channel. We can go there. There's only 18 people watching right now
Go to bed share sure night night, babe. Good night, sweetheart
Sherry, it's going to get juicier. I'll tell you about it later, but I have good dreams.
I love you so much, Sherry. Give a big ask as to if I can cloe the dog.
Yeah.
Yeah, I was just chilling here like a little villain.
Doing my own fucking thing, and I don't know why I decided
To you know share the um whole joy and go to a place where I would get kicked
That's fucking insane
Hi and relatable
We can do it all here though. I'll be too sherry. Love you a lot
Let the chaos be where it needs to be.
Good morning.
Good night. It's not morning yet, bud.
It is. It's over there. It's a little bit, uh, three in the morning where you're at or two.
Oh, right here in the West Coast.
Oh, it's on the West Coast. It's 1155. We got five minutes.
We got five minutes for the freak off to happen.
Me and Tommy again backstage like we didn't like that last time, huh?
You're freaked out.
Just chillin man smoking some weed relaxing. What are you smoking on? So Tiva and a car
Indica
Indica wedding cake
Take a bonnet with me. I'll take a bonnet. What are you taking? Okay? You taking a pipe? Okay? I
Gotta clean my bong out at all
My bong is pretty fucking dirty too. I gotta put some fucking salt and some fucking alcohol in there and like shake that shit around
Yeah, my shit is a dude. Oh
Listen
I don't give a fuck like I was literally having a great time like page was here
We have like close to like, you know, 60 people
I was like a cycle I was a cyclist people like psyche's life
Like let's go over there. I go over there. He's fucking like, I don't know. Just kick me
but I just had to um
Go rage on him a little bit
You shouldn't you shouldn't have shouldn't have ended your lives for that for psyche
He doesn't show the same respect, you know what I mean? He thinks he's a hot shot still so
Give him some time
He'll get wrecked a little bit more and realize that it's not all about him
He's got some
When I say I'm gonna do a tarot card reading for you
I don't even do tarot card readings, but he gets so fucking irate when I say let me do a reading for you
Like right now if I say Tommy James, let me do a reading for you and he sees me doing a reading for you
He will be so mad because mine will probably be more resonating
That's you know, I don't really do readings. It's just a poetry and he gets so fucking mad because it's shit. It's like generic
Oh the ace of pentacles the tool of like pentacles like the six of whatever
dickapoles
So yeah, I'm not a fan. I'm not a fan of the whole terrible thing and I never have been
ever
I can deal with some astrology and stuff, a lot of girls like that kind of stuff, but the tarot thing like I had a friend come over and you know for the first time and the first thing they did was whip out a deck of tarot cards and try to read and it just makes me feel some type of way, you know, it's like a huge red flag for me.
Is if you pull out a tarot deck and start trying to read my read my life like on some bullshit cards
But whatever, I think that's just how I feel a
Lot of people like it. That's cool
Well, I think you can relate, like you like poetry, right?
So like poetry, you know, makes more of their songs,
it makes more sense.
Well, I can just be like in the streets of a terrace,
like Mr. Esquiz came a guy who is like golden hair
with green eyes, but he's gay.
He thinks he's got the sway and he can play the cards,
but he's the fool and at the end of the day,
I will be his darkest fucking, I don't know, we can just go along with it, you know, I mean, hey, John man TV
like
The stories that he reads or his entertainment and you know the whole trivia shit
That's fucking pull that shit out of my ass. Everybody knows
Minute he goes
Let's talk about McDonald's. Is that interesting guys? And I'm like, oh my God.
It would be interesting if he streamed it like you did and walked 16 miles just to get there.
That was pretty interesting. I like the queue.
Yeah, I like that he's, I was been telling him for a couple years to do, you know, some lives on
You know, I like seeing people do that.
We need more people in the community at scale right now.
Nobody's doing anything.
Remotely, you know what I think Tony? Um, it is still but I think that would be really cool
Is like more a lot of like where people would meet up and like actually
Conjoined that would be like it would almost be like cracking that shit up again, right? So let's say you're like let's say
hypothetically
Psyche that would crack
I'm gonna lose sight of this
But if we have for anyone but more or less like why is blackout Andy?
BGQ and Aldi and all them in the same area
But because of their little beefs or whatever you guys can't link up like like I haven't ever streamed with blogger
When I was mad at him or didn't want to fuck with him and I still for the content went and hung out with them
You guys can get it together and
Go. Do you like to fight?
What are you your Seattle boys or whatever you guys are a little bit more like Chuck's worthy or whatever
I don't know where you guys are from but
um california people like imagine blackout you really want to hang out with blackout to get
like the risk of whatever you know have him like like go back out on you he might or he might not
i mean i don't know i don't know with blackout and blackout was fucking nice to me blackout was
completely fucking calm and collected maybe he wasn't drunk or something when i was hanging
It was a pretty nice guy when I met him, he, you know, he was respectful and didn't, you know, like the first time blogger came to my house, I had to keep an eye on him.
He was trying to get in the fridge and get into things in my room. He's like a little kid, you know what I mean?
You got to kind of keep your eyes on him.
Billy, I meant that Seattle people are more trustworthy of each other. I didn't see them are more trustworthy.
Well, I don't know.
That's true
People in Vegas and California are a little bit better at being fake in my opinion, but they're open
Here in the Northwest where I'm from people are a little bit more stick to themselves and their family and the few people
They know it's like not like people are scary, but people aren't really you know
People don't aren't just like down like when I lived in Vegas
You'd meet someone the same night they'd invite you to your their house and a bunch of shit people aren't scared
to like hang out and invite people to where they live and have fun but you know that's a little bit
more rare i think in the north last california so 2020 said that he hung out with blackout and he
was cool and but he wouldn't hang out with him again would you hang out with him again
yeah he'd hang out with blackout again i don't have any kind of fear like fear of if anything
Yeah, there's no fear on either side, I don't think.
I've never had beef with him like that, maybe a little bit, but not like.
You know, I'm not like everybody else
Everybody spends too much fighting like I said BG and Q being you know how many
Hours I've spent on panel with BQ and BG
Like just throughout the years and you guys won't you guys are afraid to like meet up with each other
I think it's cute, but it's also kind of sad, you know like meet up
It doesn't even have to be blackout and all them like it can I am because I know BG and blackout have their thing too
It their minimum Q and B G should like can't be but then all that shit went on with Q and D Gaff, which they were
Always tied. It's so stupid
It's so fucking stupid retarded this little fucking
Bunch of people I would hang out with Q
When he's calmer, I think he's gone calmer over the years
I've hang out with crazy people like people know that right
I would hang out with him since he's in Tally Beachy is a little bit different
Um, I think he's more like passive aggressive. So like meeting up with him would I think um Q is like more honest
Even though it might be crazy. Um, I definitely I was like, yeah, it would be cool to hang out with fucking Q
Yeah, and I'm down that way. I'll definitely I'll hit all of them up
But I'm down that way because I still have old to make bulls of traveling and
I'm not with a guy that fucking is known for missing women and their fucking face, you know
Like I'm not worried about Q but like BG is a whole different story like he'll like later
He's not gonna do nothing but
He's going to be like, oh, Bita had her paws all around me.
She wanted me like this and that.
Kiwi would just be had to come on your face and create,
you know, it'll be fun.
I kind of, I kind of know what I'm
dealing with with these people.
Even outside of first even outside of streaming it and making things available for content more people should
Still just hang out, you know and get you know the first time people hang out
They don't have to stream it. I understand though how this works, but I just yeah, I don't know I don't like that
It's kind of like impossible. I went on the RV and I was hoping that, you know, everybody's holding,
you know, you know how it is. Everybody's holding their selfie sticks and cameras in their face,
like, um, I'm not, I'm just there like, you know, but yeah, you will get, you will definitely get
caught on the camera by somebody.
There's no avoiding it even if me and you're streaming right now. We're just sitting here chilling
Um, eventually you're gonna get tempted like by donations or whatever. It's like, okay. She'll be that she'll be that you're gonna do it, you know
If that's the way it goes
Well people have seen you there's a lot of other people I'd like to see
Out in this shit, but no, that's cool. I I get it
I get it. I just am a fan of people just doing shit in the first place.
Like I just had my birthday the other day and I'm working a new job.
So I have shit to do.
Happy birthday, Tommy. Are you a counselor?
Yep. It was my birthday. It was on the 27th and I didn't stream or do shit.
I was so busy with like actual real life interactions with people and shit.
And everybody I know through like a little like they the people in my life made it like it was a special birthday everybody got together behind my back and really like tried to give me I guess some joy this year which is nice you know it's nice when people you have people that care about you like that and it's not just one person or nobody but.
Yeah
Anybody you didn't stream it, but happy birthday. I'm sorry like I missed it, but happy belated birthday
It's still your birthday. It's like still in the same, you know, when was it like
It was just the other day it was just my 38th birthday it was nothing special
But that's why I was surprised that everybody came over and
Everybody got together and like got me shit and like did things for me and
It was just kind of a
That doesn't happen every year
Oh Tommy, I'm sorry if I was an asshole like during your birthday. I think it was I didn't fucking know I would have been nicer
I'm just a bitch sometimes I can be a witch
But I don't really care about it because like I've been on these panels like you and everyone else for years
In a collection of years at this point
So I'm used to everybody being drunk and fighting with each other and getting into little arguments and people misunderstand
Because everybody is intoxicated
i'm used to that shit in real life and on the internet so
i don't take that i don't take it that personally i don't like
all the time i'm like okay good times was drunk they're not saying that you know i mean there's
been times you've been loaded you've like been mad at me kind of and i guess a weird area but you
were just mad well you keep like you were pressing me and you keep saying i know i do i do i do do
And pressure when you do that you will laugh when you're like
Like oh my god, I like it, but when it's like directed like towards me, I'm like fuck you Tommy fucking James
Nobody wants it directed at them. I get it
So Tommy are gonna be using like like some rap music. Are you gonna be producing like doing some fun stuff?
I don't know. I mean, I'd like to get back into...
I was kind of starting to get back into music a little bit more in art, but there's just different kinds of...
I want to make kind of different genres of music and there's different stuff I want to do with music.
I have to buy some equipment and, you know, it'll be like a little hobby. I'll be, you know...
to when doing
Blogger where my inspiration to start like rapping like a fucking like stupid ass, you know
Just for fun
Rap is good for the brain. I just yeah, I haven't really I don't write
Is regularly because I have like already a bunch of notebooks. I filled with shit that I never recorded
I have a bunch of beats that aren't recorded features that are recorded. I have music videos
I want to do I'd like to think with at some point
I'll get to where I can just do art and travel and work and travel and do
Because I used to be my whole life was just do art and then travel and work to do art and work to be able to travel to
you know
You know like I would like last time I went to Vegas and it was really cool
Like a bunch of my homies and everybody bought a bunch of merch and CDs and
You know, I kind of was able to showcase a bunch of stuff, but it's been a while since I've done any kind of like showcase or like, yeah, music's just I'll always enjoy it. But I don't know. I don't know if there's ever going to be a point at all or what's going to happen.
It's too hard to tell, especially when you're busy. Like I get busy with work, which is good. Money's good. But then, you know, that's time where you're not creating or not doing anything.
for yourself, so you got to have a little balance between work and you know, I
Don't know. I have like I have a cowboy hat. I want to decorate
Stupid like stupid
Yeah, I have like a cowboy hat some shoes I want to ride on I have a bunch of colored sharpies that just that kind of stupid stuff
I have a couple little projects, but yeah, I I hopefully I'll get back in the studio someday
I'd like to think I would
They're making fun of my rap fucking shit. Can I like uh, they're saying I should just do a diss song for 2020
Should I just um, should I do a read like, okay, let's see if we can do this
Yeah, it's just music. Yeah, I don't think they'd get mad
2020 2020 runs within us
I'll send them to the advertisers and firms
2020 with this money money
Let's see what's wrong with 2020 2020 with this funny money. He gave me your fake 20 and his nose was all runny
His wife gave me head
Okay
20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20
He's gonna help me do a little rhyming. Oh, no
Be the fucking up again
20 what the fuck you think you are you can rhyme better get on this fucking panel and show it how it's my handle
Army wants to show me how to make that booty pop in the free cup, but I ain't got not
Nostache
Belch zero nine. Okay, Tommy is your worst
Again, I was cooking up I am I gave it to my friend and his name was Sam
I am the eggs were ball green shit smelt funny had to put the plate for my buddy for
2020 give me some funny money a fake $20 bill when his nose was running
He tried to touch me.
Oh, shit.
He did? That's fucking really wrong.
He did not touch me.
Oh, that's fucking insane, Tommy.
Did you tell your mommy?
I would fucking snitch on fucking 2020 because he the fucking rat.
He goes apeshit in the dark like a fucking dark fat
He said his comment was a joke, but he was asking for Tommy James how much for a beta song this
What track we got to get that shit in range
I'm trying
I've got to be in the mood to rap. That's the only thing. I'm not either but we tried for you Tommy. We tried we tried. I mean not for you 20. We tried for you 2020. We did we did 2020 with this funny money.
It's pretty hard to like rhyme with 2020.
I'm hanging myself to this. Good job. Okay.
Yeah, I'm sure I think I think 2020 will survive
What's up George?
Yeah, I would do it I do a diss song for like yeah around 50 bucks or whatever 40 50 bucks, but
It's kind of fun to do those to be honest because it forces me to be a little creative and like
We should do it this on a psyche. Oh
Psyche, I don't even know
He would turn into a little fucking bitch ass dike he
Psyche Psyche Psyche Psyche Psyche
You shit. Yo dike he
Hey, Sean
Does he when you think like everything is like chaotic and like stormy and crazy we can come into like, you know, like, you know
Soft kind of calm waters
Like you guys think me and Tommy hate each other. No, we don't okay. No, we're good
We'll hate each other tomorrow, but for tonight we're cool
Night's fine. There's no day. There's no me. Should I do a psychic reading for you? So psyche gets upset. I
Mean, I'm I'm willing I suppose
Normally, I wouldn't be a man, but I mean if it makes sex
It's not the Persian spell. Don't worry. I know the psycho care. He's over there with like all those new people and
Tommy, all the instruments like from Tripp Cake now start with I got she got the purses
stuff.
Yeah, I know.
He still uses that little voice clip.
It's like fucking hilarious.
It's like every time he clips me, it's got your fucking name in the beginning on it.
Tommy is over there.
And then I don't know how many we were like we were like bewitched we were like I don't know and all kinds of like love episodes
All right, I'm gonna do one for Tommy
It's gonna be so much better than psyche doesn't know how to do it psyche doesn't know how to do anything great. Okay
We are Katie
Okay, think about something in your head. Don't tell me out loud, okay?
Your heart like a question, it might like be, like, not asking for your future.
It might be like a, well, or just like, just, just random, you know, general.
Just ask something in your heart and your head. Don't say it out loud, okay?
And when I say stop, just say stop.
Right.
Okay, tell me when to stop.
Let's stop.
Okay.
Wow.
Okay, I see it.
Okay.
It says on it's on the tennis so it said like
like happiness is like I
Don't know like your home and happiness. It's like your body. It's almost like you're a joyous person
Okay, that's where like your happiness and heart is okay. It says on the same of your scene like your
Um, it said that you're really, really, um, good at the ball means like you have a really like charismatic personality. Okay. You're very well-liked. Like, I don't know. People like you. Okay.
Something like that.
Um, okay. Remember this in whatever you do or whatever like that your destiny is. Okay.
Remember the name of the poet was Hlana Hlana was like your home. It's like somewhere is like home is or the hardest
I don't know or like your heart is like. I don't know, but it said like something about your family. Okay, but
They're like with you. Well, you have a really really supportive family
Despite many people that are like like have judgmental asshole families. I don't know your family
Pony but your family
Really like they just want you to be successful
They don't care what you do. Okay. They just want you to be happy. Okay, just you okay
So they're looking at you their eyes are upon you every day and they think about you
That you just do what you whatever it's like as long as it's good and safe like you know
It's almost like they're watching you like a hawk
You know that's very your family is watching you like a hawk making sure like no matter what you you're good
I don't know what that's about. Okay, so then um then actual like reading those just pretty short is called nasiat
Which means advice, okay?
Okay, I guess have further as color color like we can don't ever like listen to
People like various people
Like a lot of people are in your head and people will tell you do this and people will tell you do that, you know
don't listen to
multiple amount of people
Okay, uh, like being your own thoughts, um, be really focused on what you want.
Whatever that you're like focusing on, I don't know what it is like what you want.
Um, you're getting closer to it.
Okay, um, it's really good.
It said like, you know, just like it's almost like manifest what you want
This is like it like this. This is like
This page nasiat advice. This poet is telling you whatever you want from me
What the whatever the fuck you want. This is really really good. It's like manifestation
If you just manifested and like say you want it, you're going to get it. It doesn't you can get it very easily like
like drinking water
It's like waiting for you like your destiny is waiting for you
That's all I can tell you. That's a good read. That's a good reading. That's good stuff
That stuff I think about a lot
I feel like I don't live up to my potential.
Like there's a lot of stuff I still need to create and do
and I'm not, sometimes I'm not doing it.
I get a funk or I get off track sometimes.
But yeah, there's a lot of,
and then as far as just getting what you want,
I mean, yeah, I'm pretty good at getting the things I want,
but the things I want anybody could get
if they put the same amount of work in for it.
It's not special.
It's just, I know how to grind when I want something.
Well, you're still young, you know, but manifesting, that's what it was saying, it's almost like
envision it and manifest whatever you want, you're going to get it and you have a family
that doesn't give a fuck what you do, like not like what you do, of course they would
give a fuck if you're doing bad things, but they don't care if you're, you know, I don't
You know just moving forward and doing better your family is like right behind you. So that's really good
You know, you don't have judgmental family
And just be well, yeah, of course we should all be well
But I you know, it's just like when I see I've never seen that like when I open that where it's like literally
Let's do the same advice like it's like the name of his poetry. I sort of fucking got Tommy
This is serious fucking shit. You literally need to put your
Subconscious into your like real conscious whatever that you're dreaming about stop like looking into the star and the moon
And have been a dreamer like actually do it
And you could I used to be a lot better at that like I just go wherever I want to go and do whatever
I want to do and I still can do that, but I like I said, I think that I got a little off track
this year a couple of times and I
Mean, I'm just thankful that I don't have a bunch of possessions or like
People that hold me down, but sometimes people I mean it just depends what you want. I at this point my life
I kind of think I just don't want to really I
Don't want to do the family thing. I'm not really looking to do anything like that at this point
Sometimes I've struggled with that, but I mean it is pretty dope to just not have to deal with any like
you know
You mean like have a family like I have a like a conventional family like marriage with kids
Remember like we're
None of us on the internet are normal
Conventional people were pretty like wild at heart. We're kind of like wild beings. Some of us are crazy. Some of us are that you know
But at the same time, you never know what's gonna happen. Like I said, you're a young person like who knows, you know
I'm at peace with my decisions, but you've got to realize in not having a conventional family,
you know, you're taking a risk of dying alone and having nobody there to take care of you or give
a fuck about you. I don't think I'm going to have that problem. But yeah, I don't think it's going
to be any like animals or kids or life or anything like that. I don't want, I don't want anything
like that. There's anything that I did want it got away from me some time ago. So
I just think it's good to focus on myself I get it. I understand that because sometimes I'm like, oh, okay
Who's gonna take care of me? You know, I don't have you know, like who's gonna take care of me
but then also I know people that have like
Great-grandchildren and none of them give a fuck they're in a nursing home
Exactly you take a risk of raising a bunch of kids that might not even give a fuck about you might not even be around
I hate you. So that's another thing like I don't have those problems in my family, but I've seen it a lot
I'm lucky to have a good family who's understanding and I can tell
And he did my darkest secrets and it's I'm completely open with them kind of a thing
But uh, I think they like I I don't know the last couple years have been different
But yeah, usually I was really good at like I was always going to the studio or filming a video
We're flying out to Vegas or flying to the East coast
To record an album for a couple grand like I've done a lot of fun things
That I don't think a lot of people get to enjoy and I'd like to kind of still enjoy that
And do it for myself and you know continue to tour around and record and film and put it out
I'll probably get back a little that I still
Tommy I think I don't really know you that well
but I think you kind of are like a world like you would like to be a world traveler and just go around and like
Like see different places and like, you know, like discover these things and in like through the process
Who knows what you're gonna like me what opportunity is gonna come your way you can like
You're talented, you know people will see you you're like you have a lot of like character and charisma
I think honestly if I were you and you're single and you're young at your age
And you don't have any pets and liabilities. Fuck. Yeah, I would show I would go backpacking
I would go to like fucking different countries
You know you can just
Wing it the only thing do it the only thing that kind of keeps me in this area or like
It keeps me around is that like I do have parents and people that are getting older and I do have a fear of like I don't want to be, you know, on some wild Vegas trip for myself while like my you know it's like a fear of mine is that I'll be like.
I don't think you should go to Vegas.
I think like for you, I would go to like Cancun.
I would like go to like, I would travel, like I would go and-
Yeah, Vegas is played out.
Yeah, I gotta go somewhere.
Yeah, like go to nature, like get like in tune,
like with the nature and you know what?
Meanwhile, your parents are gonna be fine
because they know that you're gonna be like, you know,
on a little, you know, your own little adventure.
They'll be at peace.
But if you're in Vegas, I would worry as a parent, you know?
oh yeah they were they know how i like to have fun they worry about me a lot they know how i
they know i like to go to different places and experiment with different people and different
Well, that's the thing is like if I tell my dad right now and my family like I want to go and like hang out in Vegas for a while
They're gonna be worried about me
Because they know me
But if I tell them that I want to go travel Europe or I want to go to the sun that like they would support me
They'll be like, yeah, you know go on, you know, it's a whole different story now in your adventure. Yeah, you might fucking party over there, but
It's a whole different thing with them because they've been to Vegas before they know. Yeah, nobody supports certain things like that
Yeah, because they know what I doubt they're doing gamble in and be in degenerate life. So they know what that is
But once again, I don't have like I'm not like I'm not like cheating on a wife or I'm not
You know, I'm not hurting anybody when I'm out
Like I said, I'm at peace. I'm 38 years old. It's the chances that I'm going to do any of that conventional shit is extremely rare at this point, especially just with what's happened and how that kind of has gotten away from me at this point.
That's I mean
For you, you need to be in like some place that's like um serenity peace nature
Really good, you know like like like good hearted people not crazy people not in a parting place
Not in a gambling area, you know, just traveling and like meeting like, you know new
Cultures and like new people. I don't know. I can't explain. I just see you
Just being a world traveler and having an adventure not a vacation. Yeah, that's one of my happiest is when I'm traveling around
creating art
Living off of my you know off of my labor enjoying my hard earned money to do fun things and
due to enjoy myself, but
It's also there's a thing like it's fun to enjoy things with people too
Like I'd like to do more things with my best friends and
You know, there's a couple of people I'd like to reach out to more in my spare time
I just got like an e-bike and stuff
I'm gonna start riding around on and like that would be fun and
Get me out a little bit more. I haven't really I just got it charged in shit. I haven't I
Haven't written at one time and I've had it since my birthday
Well, don't I keep saying you're young. Fuck the past or whatever. I like you starting a new page. Um, everything is going to be like what you want. Your destiny is in your hands. So, um, you just do what makes you happy. Look at this. Okay.
Okay, how beautiful this is is this really is it? Yeah, I can like um look at it right now and find out
But all of the scenery is here
Yeah, this is what we should be experiencing. These are different places in the fucking world instead of like, okay
We've seen Vegas. We've been to fucking like Disneyland
We've been to we can go to Miami and see like women with big asses, you know
But I think for you, I think it's and for me a lot of us like even gymnics. We're you know, kind of like
Earthy people earthy
But yeah, I mean, and I don't want to get too much into it. I know you probably come boring new to second desk
Yeah, you just go here and you I don't know you walk around like you sit here
Like by the rocks and then you write and then you draw like this whole scenery
That's what life is about, you know, not about like partying is fun. All of that
You know, you can have a like a little bit of like smoke a little doobie
You can have a little bit of beer or like wine or whatever, but
People like me and you have like super addictive personality
It's just gonna you know, I'm addicted to the internet. I'm addicted to alcohol, you know
really good natural life. Look at this one. I enjoy a lot of wholesome things too. I haven't
taken a trip anywhere for like a couple of years. It's been the last time I did anything.
I already would have, Tommy. I would have, but I have tests. I got this motherfucker right here.
Karen at me. Yeah
Yeah, I got this one right here. Do you think like a cute little baby like otherwise?
I would be traveling yesterday. I would already been out of here. I
Would have been gone like I would be traveling
Yeah, that's what I'm happiest and happiest on the road on the travel
Every day life is boring and Monday all that just work to come home to sleep
So it's nice to reward yourself. And yeah with I like camping
I went out of the camp a couple times already this summer and fished and
Done some good wholesome stuff. There's a lot of that in the Northwest
To do and where I'm at so
Yeah, I love camping too. I really like camping. I need to go grab some more weed
In order to meet someone new you got to put yourself out there like go to church bars and no
HQ we're not talking about love. We're just talking about um, I don't think um me or Tommy or like
Seeking what we're just talking about on basically
Yeah, I don't know what would make us like at peace and happy because the fuck that this is like internet shit is like stupid
It's literally a waste of fucking energy and time. It is fun. It's like highly addictive, but no not love
You can't find love on the internet
And I don't even believe in like
Internet dating like what do you call it? Um, um, like what do you call that when they go on those dating sites? That's crazy
That's people meet in person a lot more last year than they still do, but it's the best now.
Yeah, the men are always looking for booty calls.
And I'm not excited that I've met real love on like, what are they?
Tender?
Not tender.
What's that one?
Oh, e-harmonie.
Tender?
The one that you have to pay for?
Tender is more like seems like the hookup thing plenty of fish people are and stuff like that
You can do free trials and people try to meet people but you better bet people and like stuff like that like you can't just keep
You know meeting the same kind of people letting them tell you the same kind of shit
Because they want to hit
That's a whole other thing
But the my thing is people trying to meet people on YouTube on these panels like Karl and in blogger and everyone else
I'm just saying the the simping and like on page and all that is just ridiculous off
Pages nice to look at she's nice and everything. I'm not putting her down at all
I'm just saying that YouTube isn't a place to come on here and like I
Don't know
I don't know maybe it's different from other people but there's a lot of I see a lot of that now when I watch these
Panels it's like drunk guys on here thinking they're gonna find a girl on a panel or something. I don't know
Well, it's kind of like um different with peach. She's kind of like a rare gem. You understand like she's kind of like
Um, especially on the internet, you're like, whoa, so she's going to be like hot commodity.
So I understand like where a lot of guys like definitely are into page.
She is absolutely amazing.
But the rest of it, I don't understand like the rest of it is just sucking bullshit.
And page is not ready anyway, she just like, you know, trying to get her life together.
I mean, don't get me wrong, you can meet people off of YouTube just like anywhere else.
I've met people off YouTube and spent time with them at least three times.
So I know about this, you know, in real life, it's, it's different if you actually go meet
the person though, like it's way different if you meet them on here and then plan to
but I think a lot of people just leave it up to oh I just want someone to talk to
they'll oh well I just want to do this long distance YouTube dating thing it's it is weird it's
everybody does it a lot of chatters do it a lot of the streamers do it I'm not putting it down
I'm just saying that I mean I guess you could meet someone anywhere but the likely of meeting
anyone on YouTube and it working out you know it's rare it's rare anyway it's supposed to be rare
Yeah, despite like what people think like I'm a super fucking slut and a whore
Carl lives like 30 minutes away from me, you know, and I never met him because
Pretty much like maybe like being on the internet with my if my way of like protecting myself
I'm like meeting people in real life because I'm like not ready. I don't want it
Like I don't know whether I've been like just like got a wall up or whatever, but I
Don't know I'd like I'm looking for excuses all the time. It could be someone's fucking shoe that can bother me and I'm just like
I'm like
It depends. It depends on the mood. That's why I haven't been streaming a lot either is because I've been trying to quit smoking cigarettes
So I've been like edgy a lot of the time
So like I have a little vape and I still smoke a couple cigarettes a day
But yeah, I've pretty much quit chain smoking. I would have easily smoked like five cigarettes by now just sit here
That's good. I'm proud of you
Night time night time
Hey, what's up, Bita? I used to be here at night time.
You were.
I think I remember this guy, he's joined my panel late at night a few times.
Yeah, Tommy, I was going to ask you, bro, I used to smoke that much cigarettes too, bro.
I used to lose count of that shit.
What kind of like cigarettes did you guys smoke?
I used to smoke the Marble Reds 100s.
Yeah.
Yeah, saying here pretty much marb red 100s. Yeah
Or anything full flavored
But yeah, I
You know I'm trying to be some damage control. I've done too much
I've done too much to not have it bite me in the ass. So I'm gonna try to be a little healthy for a while and
You know
that's a good job. Yeah, bro, and you at least like move to like vaping or something like that.
Yeah, I got a little I got a little deep bar. I've been hitting it kind of works.
Yeah, because you smoke a lot of cigarettes, bro. I watch you too. Shit.
One after another, man. Five in a row. Easy every time.
Like I would easily smoke a cart and a week easy. That's not even hard to do
So yeah, I'm trying to cut that out trying to cut the smoking out cut some
milk out and some diet stuff that was kind of making it hard for me to
Lose a couple of pounds in the summertime here. I'm doing I'm feeling healthy now though. I'm doing good now
But uh, I can change that can change quick
Okay
So I'm gonna be thankful. I got a lot of good things set up for myself. I have a
I have an interview for our hospital job actually tomorrow morning, so
It's just trying to get a step up from what I'm doing now. It just pays better
So hey, that's what's up dumb shit
I'm trying to get some of these companies that'll pay you 25 bucks an hour, you know what I mean?
Yeah, I don't want to make minimum wage and I'm trying to make, that's my goals now, like we were talking earlier, just trying to stack that money
so I can maybe create some art, maybe travel a little bit more.
You can make some fun plans for myself.
Yeah, I like that. That's good. That is my plan. I see, I see like, um, I see you like you flew away
night time. I see you being like a traveler. I don't know. I really do. Look at this. Look at
this old shirt that I have. Like, look how bad I used to be. This is every one of those is me
I don't know if you can even see look at all this. It's okay. It's comfortable. Yeah, I saw a couple. No, no, it's uh, it's uh
It's fashion. It's fashion. Look at that though. That's not
You know my ex like my ex used to have a shirt that was all like I think he bought it as Zara
And it was like the same design
You know, you know, Jack, that's why I didn't throw it away.
I looked at it like, I'm like, this shit's pretty cool.
Like, put like a different color.
I'll put like a red or a white shirt on underneath.
And it'll look cool with all the little holes.
So, yeah, actually, I'm an R.
I'm a closed, I'm a fashion designer now.
It is taking me about one good binge to get you a shirt.
How much for that shirt?
I would sell this day.
You gotta put your cologne on it on Sunday, Chimmy.
I can sell them on you. You can sell anything on eBay show. I don't sell that. I'm just kidding with you
I'll try if I say is Tommy James's they will probably I can put it on
option
nobody's nobody's trying to buy Tommy James things in 2025
Belville is gonna put 15 on it right away
I remember when Prisco Anne was supposed, like, she wanted to sell, like, her dolls all over and grows whatever their names were.
You know the dolls you should she should have sold those or should sell yeah, but she asked me
She's like Peter. Can you put on eBay for me?
Then I looked them up and I was like well
That's how much they go for and then she was like but she wanted like four times the price because she said they were like
Associated to the car reverse and I was like like you think eBay people know that fucking shit like
That's a very small, that's a small niche, niche crowd right there.
I remember that.
I remember when everybody used to troll Aaron and watch Aaron, that was, that was some fun
times too.
I chilled, um, Eric, and that's only not too harshly, very innocently.
Oh, Eric's about the most unlikable fucking person in the world, some of these people. Oh, my God.
What happened?
Oh, nothing. I'm just, you know, I'm just restless. I have to be up at, like,
I have to be up and be some to leave somewhere like eight in the morning, but I just I could not sleep and I just wanted to
Well get some sleep right now. I can't I'm gonna smoke. I'm gonna smoke
I'm gonna stay up and smoke some weeds, but yeah, I am gonna have to like lay back down
I think yeah lay down and just like I would like
Turn off the lights and just freaking listen to like some kind of guided meditation or some shit like that
Yeah, get some sleep. Just relax
get your eight hours in or seven hours or six hours stick to vaping less um thanks for letting me come on though man and
of course Tommy of course all right I want to end the live too thank you for being up here with me I'm like just keeping me company
no I'm having a good conversation yeah have a good night Pete I'll y'all see you around
Yeah, peace out.
Barber of energy.
Good night.
Bye.
Okay, guys.
See?
We can have like a good night and good convo.
When you said best of luck to Tommy, Filzy said shower again.
You want me to go take a shower?
Okay.
I'll go take a shower.
Again.
How many times should I shower?
I'll shower tomorrow again, okay?
Just for you, Filzy.
Anyways, guys, thanks for being there 2020.
The chances of me talking to thank you about whatever the fuck happened with you and why you got found are very slim coming from my part.
Hopefully Christine can come through, but at this point, fuck him because I mean, as far as like my side goes, he's like such an ungrateful asshole.
I don't give a fuck anyway.
if you guys like you know work it out all good for you um i'm sticking tired of it i i don't know
i think it's insanity that i just keep on like i don't know he thinks it's like kind of funny to
Have a little bit of fucking like respect for me because I ended my stupid panel to go over there
Paige was with me and she was my witness. She was like, yeah, let's go over there
And then we go over there and he's like being a fucking douchebag and by the way
Two people are no longer allowed on my panel
One of them is buried a turtle, but he didn't really do anything wrong. It's just by default and like, you know
um for the um purpose and the cause of the the better cause of everybody and then also alexander
mcqueen who is absolutely uh fucking vile screamer and dox says and i don't want to say i don't even
know was i i kind of know but fuck him so good night guys was i'm gonna go brush my teeth wash
Thanks for the ones that were here.